podcastchart.com 2016-11-25

# Privacy - Podcast Chart

This Policy applies as between you, the User of this Website and Project Fantastic Ltd, the owner and provider of this Website. This Policy applies to our use of any and all Data collected by us in relation to your use of the Website.

Definitions and Interpretation 

In this Policy the following terms shall have the following meanings: 

Data means collectively all information that you submit to Project Fantastic Ltd via the Website. This definition shall, where applicable, incorporate the definitions provided in the Data Protection Act 1998; 

Cookie means a small text file placed on your computer by this Website when you visit certain parts of the Website and/or when you use certain features of the Website. Details of the cookies used by this Website are set out in Clause 12; 

Project Fantastic Ltd means Project Fantastic Ltd, owners of Podcast Chart, of 86-90 Paul Street, London, EC2A 4NE; 

UK and EU Cookie Law means the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003 as amended by the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) (Amendment) Regulations 2011; 

User means any third party that accesses the Website and is not employed by Project Fantastic Ltd and acting in the course of their employment; and 

Website means the website that you are currently using (podcastchart.com) and any sub-domains of this site unless expressly excluded by their own terms and conditions. 

Scope of this Policy 

This Policy applies only to the actions of Project Fantastic Ltd and Users with respect to this Website. It does not extend to any websites that can be accessed from this Website including, but not limited to, any links we may provide to social media websites. 

Data Collected 

Without limitation, any of the following Data may be collected by this Website from time to time: name, date of birth, gender, job title, profession, contact information such as email addresses and telephone numbers, demographic information such as post code, preferences and interests, financial information such as credit / debit card numbers, IP address (automatically collected), web browser type and version (automatically collected), operating system (automatically collected), a list of URLs starting with a referring site, your activity on this Website, and the site you exit to (automatically collected). 

Our Use of Data 

Any personal Data you submit will be retained by Project Fantastic Ltd for the duration of your membership plus six (6) months. 

Unless we are obliged or permitted by law to do so, and subject to Clause 5, your Data will not be disclosed to third parties. This does not include our affiliates and / or other companies within our group. 

All personal Data is stored securely in accordance with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998. For more details on security see Clause 11 below. 

Any or all of the above Data may be required by us from time to time in order to provide you with the best possible service and experience when using our Website. Specifically, Data may be used by us for the following reasons: internal record keeping; improvement of our products / services; transmission by email of promotional materials that may be of interest to you; contact for market research purposes which may be done using email, telephone, fax or mail. Such information may be used to customise or update the Website. 

Third Party Websites and Services 

Project Fantastic Ltd may, from time to time, employ the services of other parties for dealing with matters that may include, but are not limited to, payment processing, delivery of purchased items, search engine facilities, advertising and marketing. The providers of such services have access to certain personal Data provided by Users of this Website. 

Any Data used by such parties is used only to the extent required by them to perform the services that Project Fantastic Ltd requests. Any use for other purposes is strictly prohibited. Furthermore, any Data that is processed by third parties shall be processed within the terms of this Policy and in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998. 

Links to Other Websites 

This Website may, from time to time, provide links to other websites. Project Fantastic Ltd has no control over such websites and is in no way responsible for the content thereof. This Policy does not extend to your use of such websites. Users are advised to read the privacy policy or statement of other websites prior to using them. 

Changes of Business Ownership and Control 

Project Fantastic Ltd may, from time to time, expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale and/or the transfer of control of all or part of Project Fantastic Ltd. Data provided by Users will, where it is relevant to any part of our business so transferred, be transferred along with that part and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this Policy, be permitted to use the Data for the purposes for which it was originally supplied to us. 

In the event that any Data submitted by Users is to be transferred in such a manner, you will be contacted in advance and informed of the changes. 

Controlling Use of Your Data 

Wherever you are required to submit Data, you may be given options to restrict our use of that Data. This may include the following: 

use of Data for direct marketing purposes; and 

sharing Data with third parties. 

Your Right to Withhold Information 

You may access certain areas of the Website without providing any Data at all. However, to use all features and functions available on the Website you may be required to submit certain Data. 

You may restrict your internet browser’s use of Cookies. For more information see Clause 12. 

Accessing your own Data 

You have the right to ask for a copy of any of your personal Data held by Project Fantastic Ltd (where such data is held) on payment of a small fee which will not exceed £10GBP. 

Security 

Data security is of great importance to Project Fantastic Ltd and to protect your Data we employ suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure Data collected via this Website. 

Cookies 

This Website may place and access certain first party Cookies on your computer. First party cookies are those placed directly by Project Fantastic Ltd via this Website and are used only by Project Fantastic Ltd. Project Fantastic Ltd uses Cookies to improve your experience of using the Website and to improve our range of products and services. Project Fantastic Ltd has carefully chosen these Cookies and has taken steps to ensure that your privacy is protected and respected at all times. 

By using this Website you may receive certain third party Cookies on your computer. Third party cookies are those placed by websites and/or parties other than Project Fantastic Ltd. Third party cookies are used on this Website for analytic purposes. These cookies are not integral to the services provided by the Website. 

All Cookies used by this Website are used in accordance with current UK and EU Cookie Law. 

You may, if you wish, deny consent to the placing of Cookies; however certain features of the Website may not function fully or as intended. 

Certain features of the Website depend upon Cookies to function. UK and EU Cookie Law deems these Cookies to be “strictly necessary”. Your consent will not be sought to place these Cookies. You may still block these cookies by changing your internet browser’s settings. 

This Website uses analytics services provided by Google. Website analytics refers to a set of tools used to collect and analyse usage statistics, enabling us to better understand how Users use the Website. This, in turn, enables us to improve the Website and the products and services offered through it. You do not have to allow us to use these Cookies, however whilst our use of them does not pose any risk to your privacy or your safe use of the Website, it does enable us to continually improve our business. 

The analytics services used by this Website use Cookies to gather the required information. Certain of these Cookies may be placed immediately when you decide to visit the Website and it may not be possible to obtain your prior consent. You may remove these Cookies and prevent future use of them by changing the settings in your internet browser. 

You can choose to enable or disable Cookies in your internet browser. Most internet browsers also enable you to choose whether you wish to disable all cookies or only third party cookies. By default, most internet browsers accept Cookies but this can be changed. For further details, please consult the help menu in your internet browser. 

You can choose to delete Cookies at any time however you may lose any information that enables you to access the Website more quickly and efficiently including, but not limited to, personalisation settings. 

It is recommended that you ensure that your internet browser is up-to-date and that you consult the help and guidance provided by the developer of your internet browser if you are unsure about adjusting your privacy settings. 

Changes to this Policy

Project Fantastic Ltd reserves the right to change this Policy as we may deem necessary from time to time or as may be required by law. Any changes will be immediately posted on the Website and you are deemed to have accepted the terms of the Policy on your first use of the Website following the alterations.
